Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- CSEA Publications, 1932-2014; 5; 15.04 cubic ft. 2686 Digital Files
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 June 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 June 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 June 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 June 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 June 30
  - The State Employee, 1942 June
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 July 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 July 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 July 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 July 28
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 August 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 August 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 August 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 August 25
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 September 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 September 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 September 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 September 22
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 September 29
  - The State Employee, 1942 September
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 October 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 October 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 October 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 October 27
  - The State Employee, 1942 October
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 November 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 November 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 November 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 November 24
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 December 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 December 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 December 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 December 22
  - Civil Service Leader, 1942 December 29
  - The State Employee, 1942 December
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 January 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 January 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 January 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 January 26
  - The State Employee, 1943 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 February 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 February 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 February 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 February 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 March 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 March 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 March 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 March 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 March 30
  - The State Employee, 1943 March
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 April 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 April 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 April 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 April 27
  - The State Employee, 1943 April
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 May 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 May 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 May 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 May 25
  - The State Employee, 1943 May
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 June 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 June 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 June 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 June 22
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 June 29
  - The State Employee, 1943 June
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 July 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 July 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 July 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 July 27
  - Plain Talk, Suffolk Welfare Unit Newsletter, 1943 July (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 August 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 August 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 August 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 August 24
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 August 31
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 September 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 September 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 September 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 September 28
  - The State Employee, 1943 September
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 October 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 October 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 October 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 October 26
  - The State Employee, 1943 October
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 November 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 November 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 November 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 November 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 November 30
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 December 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 December 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 December 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1943 December 28
  - The State Employee, 1943 December
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 January 11 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 January 4 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 January 11 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 January 18 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 January 25 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1944 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 February 1 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 February 8 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 February 15 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 February 22 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 February 29 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1944 February
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 March 7 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 March 14 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 March 21 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 March 28 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 April 4 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 April 11 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 April 18 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 April 25 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1944 April
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 May 2 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 May 9 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 May 16 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 May 23 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 May 28 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 May 30 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 June 6 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 June 13 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 June 20 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 June 27 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1944 June
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 July 4 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 July 11 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 July 18 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 July 25 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 August 1 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 August 8 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 August 15 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 August 22 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 August 29 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 September 5 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 September 12 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 September 19 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 September 26 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1944 September
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 October 3 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 October 10 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 October 17 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 October 24 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 October 31 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 November 7 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 November 14 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 November 21 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 November 28 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1944 November
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 December 5 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 December 12 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 December 19 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1944 December 26 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 January 2 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 January 9 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 January 16 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 January 23 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 January 30 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1945 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 February 6 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 February 13 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 February 20 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 February 27 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1945 February
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 March 6 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 March 13 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 March 20 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 March 27 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 April 3 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 April 10 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 April 17 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 April 24 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1945 April
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 May 1 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 May 8 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 May 15 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 May 22 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 May 29 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 June 5 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 June 12 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 June 19 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 June 26 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1945 June
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 July 3 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 July 10 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 July 17 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 July 24 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 July 31 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 August 7 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 August 14 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 August 21 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 August 28 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 September 4 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 September 11 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 September 18 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 September 25 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 October 2 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 October 9 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 October 16 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 October 23 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 October 30 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1945 October
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 November 6 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 November 13 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 November 20 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 November 27 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 December 4 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 December 11 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 December 18 (Reel 1)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1945 December 25 (Reel 1)
  - The State Employee, 1945 December
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 January 1 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 January 8 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 January 15 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 January 22 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 January 29 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 February 5 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 February 12 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 February 19 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 February 26 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 February
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 March 5 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 March 12 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 March 19 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 March 26 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 March
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 April 2 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 April 9 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 April 16 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 April 23 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 April 30 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 April
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 May 7 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 May 14 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 May 21 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 May 28 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 May
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 June 4 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 June 11 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 June 18 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 June 25 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 June
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 July 2 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 July 9 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 July 16 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 July 23 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 July 30 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 August 6 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 August 13 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 August 20 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 August 27 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 September 3 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 September 10 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 September 17 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 September 24 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 September
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 October 1 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 October 8 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 October 15 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 October 22 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 October 29 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 October
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 November 5 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 November 12 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 November 19 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 November 26 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1946 November-1946 December
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 December 3 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 December 10 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 December 17 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 December 24 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1946 December 31 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 January 7 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 January 14 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 January 21 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 January 28 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1947 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 February 4 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 February 11 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 February 18 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 February 25 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1947 February
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 March 4 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 March 11 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1947 March-1947 April
  - The State Employee, 1947 May-1947 June
  - The State Employee, 1947 July-1947 August
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 September 16 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 September 23 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 September 30 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1947 September
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 October 7 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 October 14 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 October 21 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 October 28 (Reel 2)
  - The State Employee, 1947 October-1947 December
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 November 4 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 November 11 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 November 18 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 November 25 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 December 2 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 December 9 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 December 16 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 December 23 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1947 December 30 (Reel 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 January 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 January 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 January 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 January 27
  - The State Employee, 1948 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 February 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 February 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 February 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 February 24
  - The State Employee, 1948 February
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 March 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 March 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 March 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 March 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 March 30
  - The State Employee, 1948 March
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 April 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 April 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 April 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 April 27
  - The State Employee, 1948 April
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 May 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 May 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 May 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 May 25
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 June 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 June 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 June 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 June 22
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 June 29
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 July 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 July 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 July 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 July 27
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 August 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 August 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 August 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 August 24
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 August 31
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 September 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 September 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 September 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 September 28
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 October 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 October 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 October 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 October 26
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 November 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 November 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 November 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 November 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 November 30
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 December 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 December 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 December 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1948 December 28
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 January 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 January 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 January 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 January 25
  - The State Employee, 1949 January
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 February 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 February 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 February 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 February 22
  - The State Employee, 1949 February
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 March 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 March 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 March 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 March 29
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 April 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 April 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 April 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 April 26
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 May 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 May 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 May 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 May 24
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 May 31
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 June 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 June 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 June 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 June 28
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 July 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 July 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 July 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 July 26
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 August 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 August 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 August 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 August 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 August 30
  - Civil Service Leader, 1949 September 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 March 14 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 March 21 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 March 28 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 April 4 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 April 11 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 April 18 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 April 25 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 May 2 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 May 9 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 May 16 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 May 23 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 May 30 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 June 6 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 June 13 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 June 27 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 July 4 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 July 11 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 July 18 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 July 25 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 August 1 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 August 8 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 August 15 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 August 22 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 August 29 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1950 September 5 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 January 2 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 January 9 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 January 16 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 January 23 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 January 30 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 February 6 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 February 13 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 February 20 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 February 27 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 March 6 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 March 13 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 March 20 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 March 27 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 April 3 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 April 10 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 April 17 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 April 24 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 May 1 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 May 8 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 May 15 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 May 22 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 May 29 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 June 5 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 June 12 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 June 19 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 June 26 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 July 3 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 July 10 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 July 17 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 July 24 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 July 31 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 August 7 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 August 14 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 August 21 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 August 28 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 September 4 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 September 11 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 September 18 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 September 25 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 October 2 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 October 9 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 October 16 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 October 23 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 October 30 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 November 6 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 November 13 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 November 20 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 November 27 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 December 4 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 December 11 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 December 18 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1951 December 25 (Reel 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 January 1 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 January 8 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 January 15 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 January 22 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 January 29 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 February 5 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 February 12 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 February 19 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 February 26 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 March 4 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 March 11 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 March 18 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 March 25 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 April 1 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 April 8 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 April 15 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 April 22 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 April 29 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 May 6 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 May 13 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 May 20 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 May 27 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 June 3 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 June 10 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 June 17 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 June 24 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 July 1 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 July 8 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 July 15 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 July 22 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 July 29 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 August 5 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 August 12 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 August 19 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 August 26 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 September 2 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 September 9 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 September 16 (Reel 4)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1952 September 23 (Reel 4)